

Contact

(+34) 605 603 063

 \searrow

r.mir.min@activicat.cat

 $\mathfrak Q$

Barcelona, Spain



github.com/roger-mir-min

in

<u>linkedin.com/in/roger-mir-min</u>

Languages

- Catalan, Spanish, French: native
- English: C2 (CPE)
- German: B1
- Polish: A2

Hard skills

- HTML, CSS, JS (ES6)
- SASS, TypeScript
- Angular (2 16), React
- WordPress (WooCommerce)
- Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Angular Material
- jQuery, Leaflet, DataTables
- Testing: Jasmine, Karma
- Node.js, MySQL, AWS, Firebase
- Git, Github

Soft skills

- Detailed analysis
- Problem-solving
- Organization
- Teamwork
- Communication skills
- Adaptability
- Initiative
- Self-learning

Roger Miret

Frontend Developer

Angular-specialized, I also work with React and WordPress, and when needed I adapt to build Backend. My journey in programming began as a self-taught enthusiast while working as a teacher of Catalan language and culture. In 2022 I chose to turn my passion into a professional path by enrolling in an Angular bootcamp. Currently I work as a freelancer while continuing to study web technologies.

Education

'Front End Angular' bootcamp (IT Academy, Barcelona) - 640h November 2022 - May 2023

'Angular from scratch to expert' (Udemy - F. Herrera) - 44h January - March 2023

Degree and Master's in Catalan Philology (Universitat de Barcelona) 2013 - 2019

Master's in Language and Literature Didactics (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona)

2017 - 2018

Experience

Full Stack Developer (freelance)

August 2023 - Present

- Development of a website for a professional psychologist, with admin interface. Angular (Service Workers, Kolkov), Tailwind CSS, Firebase. Performance, SEO & accessibility criteria applided.
- Development of two personal websites for a client. Wordpress. In development.

Frontend Developer at IT Academy (internship)

July 2023

- Frontend Development for a programming exercises website: layout creation and logic implementation from a Figma design. Angular, NgBootstrap.
- Unit & integration testing with Jasmine and Karma.
- Agile/ SCRUM methodology; coordination with Frontend, Designers and Backend teams (15-member team in total) through Github (pull requests, Gitflow workflow).

Full Stack Developer at IT Academy (internship)

March - June 2023

- Full Stack design for a Catalan language exercises webpage, with register for students and teachers, groups management, homework, history, progress tracking...
- Angular, NgBootstrap, Angular Material, DataTables, Node.js, MySQL, AWS hosting.

Catalan Language and Culture teacher

2021 - 2022: Teacher of recently immigrated students at INS Dolors Aleu (Barcelona).

2019 - 2021: Adjunct professor at Uniwersytet im. Adama Mickiewicza (Poznań).

2018 - 2019: Teacher at INS Galileo Galilei (Barcelona).

- Dynamic teaching methods, constant adaptability to changing groups.
- Coordination with pedagogical and psychopedagogical teams.
- Cultural facilitation (conversation groups, workshops and event organization).

Proofreader and Editor (freelance)

2017 - 2020

Corrections for individuals. Edition of *El Poema del Bosc* (A. de Riquer), ed. Adesiara: according edition criteria, thoroughly reviewing and adapting the text; researching about the work, author, and context; writing the foreword and footnotes.